[
  {
    "question": "We play tennis at 9 o'clock tomorrow.",
    "correctAnswers": ["We will be playing tennis at 9 o'clock tomorrow."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "My sister celebrate her birthday next week.",
    "correctAnswers": ["My sister will be celebrating her birthday next week."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "I work late at the office tonight.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I will be working late at the office tonight."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "We swim in the pool at 8 o'clock tonight.",
    "correctAnswers": ["We will be swimming in the pool at 8 o'clock tonight."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "We play football on the field at 7 o'clock tonight.",
    "correctAnswers": ["We will be playing football on the field at 7 o'clock tonight."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "I wait for you at the restaurant at 6 o'clock.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I will be waiting for you at the restaurant at 6 o'clock."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "My mum water the plants in the morning.",
    "correctAnswers": ["My mum will be watering the plants in the morning."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "I travel to Japan next month.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I will be travelling to Japan next month."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "The children play in the park in the evening.",
    "correctAnswers": ["The children will be playing in the park at 6 o'clock in the evening."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "Some students do their homework at the library tonight.",
    "correctAnswers": ["Some students will be doing their homework at the library tonight."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "The birds sing in the morning.",
    "correctAnswers": ["The birds will be singing in the morning."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "My sister dust the furniture in her room tomorrow morning.",
    "correctAnswers": ["My sister will be dusting the furniture in her room tomorrow morning."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "I watch a horror movie tonight.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I will be watching a horror movie tonight."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "Our teacher teach us grammar tomorrow.",
    "correctAnswers": ["Our teacher will be teaching us grammar tomorrow."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "She wear a T-shirt to the party tonight.",
    "correctAnswers": ["She will be wearing a T-shirt to the party tonight."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "The farmer feed the pigs in the morning.",
    "correctAnswers": ["The farmer will be feeding the pigs in the morning."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "My father read a newspaper after work.",
    "correctAnswers": ["My father will be reading a newspaper after work."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "She take her yoga class next week.",
    "correctAnswers": ["She will be taking her yoga class next week."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have dinner with my family at 8 o'clock tonight.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I will be having dinner with my family at 8 o'clock tonight."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "My father have a business meeting at 4 o'clock.",
    "correctAnswers": ["My father will be having a business meeting at 4 o'clock."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "I visit my friend at his house tonight.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I will be visiting my friend at his house tonight."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "We have coffee in this cafe tomorrow morning.",
    "correctAnswers": ["We will be having coffee in this cafe tomorrow morning."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "We will be having coffee in this cafe tomorrow morning.",
    "correctAnswers": ["We will be having coffee in this cafe tomorrow morning."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "I go to the theatre at 6 o'clock tomorrow.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I will be going to the theatre at 6 o'clock tomorrow."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "We fly to London next month.",
    "correctAnswers": ["We will be flying to London next month."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "We go on a picnic with our friends on Saturday.",
    "correctAnswers": ["We will be going on a picnic with our friends on Saturday."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "The children study for their English exam tonight.",
    "correctAnswers": ["The children will be studying for their English exam tonight."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "My mum cook fish for dinner tonight.",
    "correctAnswers": ["My mum will be cooking fish for dinner tonight."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "She work from home next Thursday.",
    "correctAnswers": ["She will be working from home next Thursday."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "He play computer games at 11 o'clock.",
    "correctAnswers": ["He will be playing computer games at 11 o'clock."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "My sister do shopping tomorrow morning.",
    "correctAnswers": ["My sister will be doing shopping tomorrow morning."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "The photographer take pictures of our family this Sunday.",
    "correctAnswers": ["The photographer will be taking pictures of our family this Sunday."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "We leave the house in ten minutes.",
    "correctAnswers": ["We will be leaving the house in ten minutes."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "She use my computer for work tomorrow.",
    "correctAnswers": ["She will be using my computer for work tomorrow."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "The doctor see patients tomorrow morning.",
    "correctAnswers": ["The doctor will be seeing patients tomorrow morning."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "The cat sleep all day long.",
    "correctAnswers": ["The cat will be sleeping all day long."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "The blogger make a new video next week.",
    "correctAnswers": ["The blogger will be making a new video next week."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "I walk with my dog at 6 o'clock tomorrow.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I will be walking with my dog at 6 o'clock tomorrow."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "We run in the park on Friday.",
    "correctAnswers": ["We will be running in the park on Friday."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "I write a letter to my friend tonight.",
    "correctAnswers": ["I will be writing a letter to my friend tonight."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  },
  {
    "question": "They move to New York next year.",
    "correctAnswers": ["They will be moving to New York next year."],
    "punctuationMark": ".",
    "typePrompt":"futureContinuous"
  }
]